<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Random | Ellison Leão]]></title>
  <link href="http://ellisonleao.github.com/blog/categories/random/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ellisonleao.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-13T19:14:35-02:00</updated>
  <id>http://ellisonleao.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ellison Leão]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ellisonleao@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hope of our childhood isn't lost (yet)]]></title>
    <link href="http://ellisonleao.github.com/blog/2012/a-infancia-ainda-nao-esta-perdida/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-16T12:33:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ellisonleao.github.com/blog/2012/a-infancia-ainda-nao-esta-perdida</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Monday is usually the day you wake a little bit more lazier, hoping to spend a little more time in bed, thinking why can’t it be Friday to sleep a little more time.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, when I arrived at work I came across to a really fantastic notice. A notice that encouraged that Monday routine and made me think of my childhood, of how I loved to create things and how I imagine doing adult things. On that notice I saw a boy of nine years old creating an analogic arcade just using cardboard boxes. He created everything from the box that manages the money of the chips ($ 1 per card) and so-called fun passes (allowing a total of 500 shots for $ 2), to the games. The boy who helps his father in his mechanic garage, was discovered by a customer of the shop, who created a Facebook event and a Crowd Funding movement  to raise money for his college. The boy’s name is Caine and this short movie below was created to show all of this little boy’s geniality. Check below</p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/40000072 "></iframe></div></p>

<p><a href="http://www.updateordie.com/2012/04/11/o-menino-que-montou-um-fliperama-com-caixas-de-papelao/">Saw it here</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mute in Curitiba]]></title>
    <link href="http://ellisonleao.github.com/blog/2011/mute-em-curitiba/"/>
    <updated>2011-09-16T12:13:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ellisonleao.github.com/blog/2011/mute-em-curitiba</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the finest things about living in Curitiba is that you can go to a lots of great shows and pay really cheap tickets. On September 4th was a hardcore day in Curitiba. I went to a show with Mute ( Canada ), one of the most promissing bands of the world hardcore bands scenario. I paid about R$ 25,00 (show worth the price) , and the show was really exciting. Here some live footage</p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/aaUmOSvROBw "></iframe></div></p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/srTUn_o4WUM "></iframe></div></p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/fiXKEAOtAtI "></iframe></div></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
